Office of the President Jill Ker Conway Files, 1974-1985
Smith College Archives
- SERIES V. ADMINISTRATIVE OFFICES
  - Development
    - -Director of Development Services 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - -Endowed Chairs/Professorships 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - -Endowment Letters [sample only] 1982 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - -Foundation Advisory Committee 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - -Foundations
      - -General 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 2)
        See also Series V. Administrative Offices-Development-Corporations-General
      - -General 1977-1981 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - -Abbott Laboratories Fund 1981-1984 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - -Aetna Foundation 1975-1985 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - -Alden Trust 1975-1984 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - -Applegarth Foundation 1976-1981 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - -Atlantic Richfield Foundation 1975-1985 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - -[George F.] Baker Trust 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - -Bankers Trust 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - -Barbour Fund 1979-1982 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - -Braitmayer Foundation 1975-1983 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - -Brown Foundation 1975, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - -Brown Foundation 1981-1984 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - -Brunswick Foundation 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - -Burden Foundation 1976 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - -Bush Foundation 1976-1985 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - -Carolyn Foundation 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - -Champion International Awards 1977-1985 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - -[Edna McConnell] Clark Foundation 1975-1977 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - -[Edna McConnell] Clark Foundation 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - -[Robert Sterling] Clark Foundation 1975-1980 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - -Commonwealth Fund 1979-1985 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - -Culpeper Foundation 1976-1983 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - -Dalton Foundation 1975-1980 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - -Dana Foundation 1975-1983 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - -Dana Foundation 1984 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - -Dana Foundation 1985 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - -Donner Foundation 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - -Dreyfus Foundation 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - -Dreyfus Foundation 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - -DuPont Foundation 1976-1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - -Educational Foundation of America 1975-1977 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - -Educational Foundation of America 1978-1980 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - -Exxon Education Foundation 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - -Exxon Education Foundation 1979 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - -Exxon Education Foundation 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - -Exxon Education Foundation 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - -FIPSE 1976-1983 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - -Ford Foundation 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - -Ford Foundation 1977 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - -Ford Foundation 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - -Ford Foundation 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - -Ford Foundation 1983-1985 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - -Gaffney Foundation 1975-1979 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - -[Eva] Gebhard-Gourgand Foundation 1976 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - -General Electric Foundation 1975-1985 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - -German Marshall Fund 1976-1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - -Glenmede Trust Company 1976-1981 (Box 19, Folder 12)
        See also Series V. Administrative Offices-Development-Foundations-Pew Memorial Trust
      - -Glenmede Trust Company 1982 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - -Glenmede Trust Company 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - -Hazen Foundation 1976, 1979, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - -Hewlett Foundation 1978-1980 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - -Hewlett Foundation 1981-1985 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - -Institute for Advanced Study 1978 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - -Johnson Endeavor Foundation 1976 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - -Keck Foundation 1982-1985 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - -[Joseph P.] Kennedy, Jr. Foundation 1978-1980 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - -[Ada Howe] Kent Foundation 1975-1980 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - -[Ada Howe] Kent Foundation 1981-1985 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - -Kresge Foundation 1975-1978 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - -Kresge Foundation 1979 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - -Kresge Foundation 1980-1985 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - -[Samuel H.] Kress Foundation 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - -Lilly Endowment 1975-1981 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - -[Henry] Luce Foundation 1975-1985 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - -MacArthur Foundation 1980-1985 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - -Macy Foundation 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - -Macy Foundation 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - -Mellon Foundation 1975-1978 (Box 21, Folder 9)
        See also Series XII. Faculty & Staff-Women and Social Change Project
      - -Mellon Foundation 1980 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - -Mellon Foundation 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - -Mellon Foundation 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - -Merck Company Foundation 1975-1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - -Merck Company Foundation 1980-1984 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - -Merrill Trust 1975-1982 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - -Metropolitan Life Foundation 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - -Metropolitan Life Foundation 1977 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - -Metropolitan Life Foundation 1979-1982 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - -Mobil Foundation 1975-1982 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - -Monticello College Foundation 1975-1981 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - -Mott Foundation 1975-1978 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - -Mott Foundation 1979 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - -Mott Foundation 1980 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - -Mott Foundation 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - -Mott Foundation 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - -National Association of Bank Women 1976 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - -National Endowment for the Humanities 1976-1978 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - -National Endowment for the Humanities 1979-1983 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - -National Science Foundation 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - -National Science Foundation 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - -National Science Foundation 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - -National Science Foundation 1981-1985 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - -National Science Foundation-CAUSE Grant 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - -Olin Foundation 1976-1982 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - -Peat Maswick Mitchell Foundation 1979-1984 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - -Pew Memorial Trust 1976-1982 (Box 24, Folder 8)
        See also Series V. Administrative Offices-Development-Foundations-Glenmede Trust
      - -Pew Memorial Trust 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - -Presser Foundation 1976-1985 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - -Revlon Foundation, Inc. 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - -Rockefeller Foundation 1975-1979 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - -Rockefeller Foundation 1980-1983 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - -Schlumberger Foundation 1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - -Schumann Foundation 1975-1984 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - -Scott Paper Company Foundation 1975-1982 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - -Shell Companies Foundation 1975-1979 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - -Sloan Foundation 1975-1978 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - -Sloan Foundation 1979-1981 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - -Sloan Foundation 1982 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - -Sloan Foundation 1983 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - -Sloan Foundation 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - -Surdna Foundation 1975-1981 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - -Teagle Foundation 1975-1984 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - -Truman Scholarship 1976-1984 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - -Xerox Foundation 1976-1983 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - -Miscellaneous Foundations, A-K ca. 1975-1985 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - -Miscellaneous Foundations, L-Z ca. 1975-1985 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - -Friends of Smith College 1980-1983 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - -Fundraising Objectives 1975-1984, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - -Gift Crediting and Reporting Policies 1984 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - -Grants Officer 1976-1983 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - -Leadership Gifts Committee 1984 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - -Major Gifts Committee (Box 27)
      See Series V. Administrative Offices-Development-Resource Development Committee.
    - -New York Office 1975-1981 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - -New York Trips 1975-1983 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - -Organizational Structure 1975, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - -Parents Committee 1975-1979 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - -Parents Committee 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - -Parents Committee 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - -Parents Committee 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - -President's Committee 1976 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - -President's Committee 1977 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - -President's Committee 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - -President's Committee 1980 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - -President's Committee 1981 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - -President's Committee 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - -President's Committee 1984-1985 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - -Resource Development Committee 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - -Resource Development Committee 1982 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - -Resource Development Committee 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - -Slide Show 1976-1978 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - -Special Projects
      - -Ada Comstock Program 1975 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - -[Newton] Arvin Memorial Fund 1979-1981 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - -Asian Studies and Religion ca. 1981 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - -Athletic Facilities 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - -Botanical Facilities 1975-1983 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - -Canadian Studies 1976-1978 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - -Canadian Studies 1979 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - -Canadian Studies Jan-Jul 1980 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - -Canadian Studies Aug-Dec 1980 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - -Canadian Studies 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - -Canadian Studies Jan-Jul 1983 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - -Canadian Studies Aug-Dec 1983 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - -Canadian Studies Jan-Apr 1984 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - -Canadian Studies May-Dec 1984 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - -Canadian Studies 1985, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - -Chapel/Religious Life 1976-1984 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - -Crew 1976-1981 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - -[George] deVillafranca Memorial Fund 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - -[Alice] Dickinson Scholarship Fund 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - -Faculty Development (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - -Faculty Development-"In Support of the Faculty" 1982 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - -Financial Aid 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - -Five Colleges (Box 30)
        See Series XIV. Intercollegiate Associations-Five Colleges-Grants and Proposals
      - -John M. Greene Organ 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - -Knowles Memorial Scholarship 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - -Libraries 1976-1982 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - -Museum of Art 1982-1984, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - -Riding Stables 1985 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - -School for Social Work 1976-1985 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - -Sciences 1976-1984 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - -[Maya] Yates Fund 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - -Miscellaneous c. 1975-1985 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - -Stewardship Program 1981 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - -Tax Exemptions 1981 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - -Women's Educational Equity Act 1975-1977 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Dining Services (Box 30)
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Residence & Dining Services
  - Electronics 1975 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Environmental Health and Safety 1975-1977 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    See also Series V. Administrative Offices-Administrative Information Systems (1983-1985) for information re. Health and Safety issues for computer users
  - Financial Aid
    See also Series IX. Cttes & Bds. for a number of related committees.
    - -Annual Reports 1977-1984 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - -General 1975 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - -General 1976 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - -General 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - -General 1979 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - -General 1980 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - -General 1981 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - -General 1982 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - -General 1983 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - -General 1984 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - -General 1985 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - -Financial Aid Retreats 1981-1984 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - -Financial Aid Retreats-Background Material 1983 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - -Office Methods Ltd. Report 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - -Overlap Group 1982-1984 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - -Scholarships
      - -General 1977-1984 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - -Sophia Smith Scholarships for South African Students 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - -Jill Ker Conway Scholarship: (Box 32)
        See Series XVII. Students-Student Organizations-Student Government Association-STA
  - Food Services (Box 32)
  - Foreign Students Office 1976-1984 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Health Services
    - -Annual Reports 1975-1978 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - -Annual Reports 1979-1981 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - -Annual Reports 1982-1985 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - -General 1975-1979 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - -General 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - -General 1982-1983 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - -General 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - -Counseling Service 1975-1984 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - -Environmental Health (Box 33)
      See Series V. Administrative Offices-Environmental Health and Safety
    - -Women and Alcohol Project 1982-1983 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Human Resources (Box 33)
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Personnel
  - Institutional Research 1983 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Institutional Research 1984 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Institutional Research 1985, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Jahnige Social Science Research Center 1975-1984 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    See also Series IX. Committees & Boards-Jahnige Center Advisory Committee
  - Language Laboratory (Box 33)
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Electronics
  - Laundry 1976-1982 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Libraries
    See also Series IX. Committees & Boards-Library Committee
    - -Annual Reports 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - -Annual Reports 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - -Annual Reports 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - -Annual Reports 1981-1982 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - -Annual Reports 1983-1984 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - -General 1975-1979 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - -General 1980-1983 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - -General 1984-1985 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - -College Archives and Sophia Smith Collection
      See also Series VII. Buildings & Grounds-Alumnae Gym
      - -Annual Reports 1975-1978 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - -Annual Reports 1979-1981 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - -Annual Reports 1982-1984 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - -General 1975 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - -General 1976 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - -General 1977 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - -General 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - -General 1980 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - -General Jan-Apr 1981 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - -General May-Dec 1981 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - -General Jan-Jul 1982 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - -General Aug-Dec 1982 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - -General Jan-Jun 1983 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - -General Jul-Dec 1983 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - -General 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - -Ames Family Papers 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - -Ella Reeve Bloor Papers 1980-1982 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - -Margaret Sanger Papers 1976-1983 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - -Director Search 1983-1985 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - -"The Goals Study" 1982 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - -Goals Study Background 1982 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - -Goals Study Outline 1982 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - -McCree Report 1983 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - -"Science at Smith" course (1984) (Box 36)
        See Series III. Academic Programs-History of Science
    - -Friends of the Library 1975-1983 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - -Hillyer Art Library 1982 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - -Josten Performing Arts Library 1976-1984 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - -Library Staff Association 1976-1984 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - -Mortimer Rare Book Room
      - -General 1976-1979 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - -General 1980-1985 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - -Sylvia Plath Papers 1980-1984 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - -Neilson Library
      - -General 1976-1984 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - -Fire Protection 1975-1978 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - -Renovation Dedication 1981-1983 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - -School for Social Work Collection 1981-1983 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - -Non-Print Resource Center 1976-1985 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      See Also, Series IX. Committees & Boards -Non-Print Resource Center Committee
  - Minority Affairs (Box 36)
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Dean of the College-Assistant to the Dean for Minority Affairs -and- Series V. Administrative Offices-Dean of Students-Assistant to the Dean for Minority Students
  - Museum of Art
    - -Annual Reports 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - -Annual Reports 1976 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - -Annual Reports 1977 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - -Annual Reports 1978 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - -Annual Reports 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - -Annual Reports 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - -Annual Reports 1984-1984 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - -General 1975 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - -General Jan-Jun 1976 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - -General Jul-Dec 1976 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - -General 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - -General 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - -General 1981-1982 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - -General 1983-1985 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - News Office (Box 38)
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Secretary of the College for material before December 1980 -and- Series V. Administrative Offices-Public Relations for material after December 1980.
  - Personnel
    - -General 1975-1976 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - -General 1977-1980 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - -General 1981 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - -General 1982-1983 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - -General 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - -Benefits
      - -General 1975-1979 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - -General 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - -General 1982-1985 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - -Education Assistance Plan 1975-1977 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - -Maternity Leave 1975-1979 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - -Pension Plan 1975-1983 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - -Pension Plan-Plan Description 1978 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - -Tuition Grant 1981-1983 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - -Social Security 1979-1983 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - -Unions 1975 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - -Unions 1976 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - -Unions 1977-1985 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Physical Plant
    See also Series VII. Buildings & Grounds
    - -Annual Reports 1981-1982 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - -Annual Reports 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - -General 1975-1977 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - -General 1978-1981 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - -General 1982-1983 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - -General 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - -Air Conditioning 1976-1984 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - -Asbestos 1984 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - -Building Services Reorganization 1979 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - -Central Heating 1981-1983 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - -Energy Conservation (Box 40)
      - -General 1975-1984 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - -Program Review 1977 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - -Program Review Update 1978 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - -Maintenance Plans 1984 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Planning and Research (Box 40)
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Institutional Research
  - President's Office
    See also Series IX. Committees & Boards-President's Office/Board of Trustees, Ad Hoc Committee to Evaluate the Functions of
    - -General 1975-1979 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - -General 1980-1985 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - -Assistant to the President
      - -Charles Henderson 1975-1977 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - -Jean Higgins 1976-1979 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - -Ruth Solie 1979-1982 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - -Assistant to the President for Campus Planning 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - -Assistant to the President for Campus Planning 1979 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - -Assistant to the President for Campus Planning 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - -Assistant to the President for Campus Planning 1982-1983 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - -Christmas Cards 1977-1980 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - -President's Discretionary Fund (Box 41)
      See Series V. Administrative Offices-Treasurer-President's Discretionary Fund
    - -President's Report 1977-1985 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - -Rough Drafts 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - -Rough Drafts 1984 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Public Relations 1980-1981 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    See also Series V. Administrative Offices-Secretary of the College for material before December 1980 (the News Office and Publications fell under the Secretary of the College until December 1980)
  - Public Relations 1982 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Public Relations Jan-Jun 1983 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Public Relations Jul-Dec 1983 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Public Relations Jan-Apr 1984 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Public Relations May-Dec 1984 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Public Relations 1985, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Publications (Box 42)
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Secretary of the College for material before December 1980 and Series V. Administrative Offices-Public Relations for material after December 1980
  - Registrar
    - -General 1975-1979 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - -General 1980-1985 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - -Grade Distribution Study 1978 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - -Registrar Search 1975-1976 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Rental Properties
    See also Series IX. Cttes & Bds-Rental Properties, Advisory Ctte
    - -Annual Reports 1975-1976 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - -General 1975-1984 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - -Available Apartment Lists 1975-1985 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - -Occupancy Lists 1975-1984 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - -Taxation 1980-1982 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - -Taxation 1983 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - -Taxation 1984 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Residence and Dining Services
    - -Annual Reports 1975-1984 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - -General 1975-1979 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - -General 1980-1983 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - -General 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of the College 1975-1977 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of the College 1978-1980 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of the College 1981-1985, undated (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Security 1976-1985, undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
    See also Series XVII. Students-Violence Against -and- Series XV. Non-Smith Organizations-Assoc of Indep.Colleges and Universities in Mass. (1983-1984), for standards of campus security throughout Massachusetts
  - Special Programs (Box 44)
    See Series III. Academic Programs-Bridge Program -and- Series III. Academic Programs-I.S. 201 -and- Series IV. Admin Issues-Summer Progs
  - Treasurer
    - -Annual Report Transmittals 1975-1984 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - -General 1975 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - -General 1976 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - -General 1977 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - -General 1978 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - -General 1979-1980 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - -General 1981 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - -General Jan-Jun 1982 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - -General Jul-Dec 1982 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - -General Jan-Jul 1983 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - -General Aug-Dec 1983 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - -General Jan-Jun 1984 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - -General Jul-Sep 1984 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - -General Oct-Dec 1984 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - -General 1985 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - -Consumer Price Index 1976-1983 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - -Coopers & Lybrand [Accountants] 1981-1983 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - -President's Discretionary Fund
      - -Summaries 1975-1982 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - -Supporting Material 1975-1976 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - -Supporting Material 1977 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - -Supporting Material 1978 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - -Supporting Material 1979 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - -Supporting Material 1980 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - -Supporting Material 1981 (Box 46, Folder 3)